[
{
"ques_no": "1",
"question": "Acid in lemon is ?",
"a": "Citric",
"b": "Hydrochloric",
"c": "Sulfuic",
"d": "Nitric",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "a"
},
{
"ques_no": "2",
"question": "Which is a metal ?",
"a": "Iron",
"b": "Oxygen",
"c": "Water",
"d": "Sugar",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "a"
},
{
"ques_no": "3",
"question": "Gas we breathe out ?",
"a": "Oxygen",
"b": "Nitrogen",
"c": "Hydrogen",
"d": "Carbon Dioxide",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "4",
"question": "Murcury is ?",
"a": "Solid",
"b": "Liquid",
"c": "Gas",
"d": "None",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "5",
"question": "Atomic number of Hydrogen ?",
"a": "2",
"b": "8",
"c": "1",
"d": "10",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "6",
"question": " Water pH is ?",
"a": "6",
"b": "5",
"c": "7",
"d": "4",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "7",
"question": "Which is not a gas ?",
"a": "Oxygen",
"b": "Hydrogen",
"c": "Iron",
"d": "Nitrogen",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "C"
},
{
"ques_no": "8",
"question": "What is HCl ?",
"a": "Salt",
"b": "Base",
"c": "Acid",
"d": "Water",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "9",
"question": "Which is not a metal ?",
"a": "Iron",
"b": "Copper",
"c": "Carbon",
"d": "Silver",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "10",
"question": "Rusting happens to ?",
"a": "Wood",
"b": "Plastic",
"c": "Iron",
"d": "Glass",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
}
]